And it's your turn now. I'm going to
حان دوركم الآن. سأزودكم
provide you with some programmatic assessments to execute.
ببعض التقييمات البرمجية للتنفيذ.
And it's your job to determine which part of the results of
ومهمتك هي تحديد أي جزء من نتائج
these assessments reveal data quality issues.
هذه التقييمات يكشف عن مشكلات ذات صلة بجودة البيانات.
So the first one, series.value_counts on the patient's surname and address.
أول جزء هو، series.value_counts في اسم العائلة للمريض وعنوانه.
So I think this is a bit curious. Let's expand on that.
لذلك أعتقد أن هذا أمر غريب بعض الشيء. دعونا نتعمق في ذلك.
.duplicated reveals the duplicates in the address column.
متكرر يكشف عن التكرارات في عمود العنوان.
So I definitely see something here. I hope you do, too.
فبالتأكيد الاحظ شيئًا ما هنا. وآمل أن تلاحظوا ما أقصده.
If you don't that's okay, you'll see shortly.
ولكن إذا لم تكن تلاحظ ذلك، فلا بأس، ستلاحظ قريبًا.
And here's another programmatic assessment.
وإليك تقييم برمجي آخر.
sort_values on the weight column to the patients table.
sort_values في عمود الوزن إلى عمود المرضى.
And one more, using the.isnull method on
وآخر باستخدام طريقة isnull في أعمدة
the Auralin and Novadra columns in conjunction with sum.
Auralin وNovadra بالتزامن مع المجموع.
Okay, so please try to detect the data quality issues
والآن، يرجى محاولة استكشاف المشكلات ذات الصلة بجودة البيانات
in the following snapshots in the following quizzes.
في اللقطات التالية في الاختبارات التالية.